entrecredits.com 2011-12-29

# Entrecard

Privacy Policy  
  
(Last modified on 8/05/2009)

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our sites. This privacy policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and protect the personal information you choose to share when using our sites, and what choices you have concerning our use of such information. By using or accessing our sites, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Please read it carefully. From time to time, we may need to change this privacy policy in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what types of information we collect, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone else. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy or practices, please e-mail us at: support@Entrecard.com.

**Scope of Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy applies to your use of all of the sites and services owned or operated by Entrecard.com, and affiliated companies (collectively "Entrecard" or "we," "us," or "our"), including www.Entrecard.com and any other site that we own or operate (collectively, the "Entrecard Sites"). Unless we say otherwise, all references to the Entrecard Sites in this policy include all such sites.

Please note, however, that this policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites that you may access through links provided on the Entrecard Sites.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
When you use the Entrecard Sites, you provide us with two types of information: personal information you choose to share and non-personal information we gather as you interact with the Entrecard Sites.

Personal Information: When you register with the Entrecard Sites, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, account password and email address. We will only use such information for the purposes for which it was requested, such as for site administration, to protect your account from unauthorized access, and to contact you when necessary.

On a voluntary basis, you may choose to share additional personal information when using the Entrecard Sites, such as by customizing your profile, adding a photo, posting reviews or comments, sending messages and performing searches. Please remember that any such personal information you disclose in this way becomes public information to the extent you choose to allow other users access to it. You should exercise caution when deciding whether and what types of information you wish to disclose. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. We collect and retain this personal information or profile data so that you can utilize the unique personalized features of the Entrecard Sites. We may also use such information or data to understand how our users as a group utilize the services and resources provided on the Site, to track the demographics of our users and to collaborate with partners and advertisers. In the event, such information is disclosed to partners and advertisers it will only be in the form of aggregate data which does not describe or identify any individual user.

When you register with Entrecard, you create your own profile. They are displayed to people to enable you to connect with others on Entrecard. From time to time, we may use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding updates or new services offered by Entrecard that we think you may find valuable.

If you send the Entrecard Sites an electronic mail transmission, the email transmission is not necessarily secure and is not encrypted. Accordingly, email transmissions are not necessarily protected from unauthorized access. Transmission of email is at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for your transmission of personal information or any obligation with respect to that information not submitted over the secure server.

The Entrecard Sites allow its users to change or correct personal information previously provided. Please note, however, that even after modification or removal, residual copies of such information may remain on back-up media and may still be viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored the information.

We will not sell, rent, swap, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties for commercial purposes, with the exception of the following: If Entrecard enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, we may disclose and/or transfer your personal information to our business partners or new owners. Under these limited circumstances, your information may be sold as part of Entrecard's assets and for the purpose of allowing the new owner to continue Entrecard's operations. In any such transfer of information, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if required to do so to comply with legal process or requirements, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of others, including in the interests of fraud detection and prevention and credit risk reduction or abuses of the Entrecard service.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes and in a manner different than those described in this policy, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use and give you an opportunity to opt out of such use for those other purposes.

Non-Personal Information: We also collect non-personal information through the use of "cookies" (small text files that reside on your hard drive) and/or IP address tracking. Non-personal information might include the URL, the browser, the type of computer, the operating systems, and the Internet service providers you use, and other similar information. Our system also automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our sites and about the links you select from within our sites to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.

We use such non-personal information in the form of aggregate data (which does not describe or identify any individual user) to understand how our users as a group utilize the services and resources provided on our sites. This way we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Entrecard Sites may not function properly.

**Children Under Age 13**  
The Entrecard Sites do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13, or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Entrecard Sites. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or to send any information about yourself to us. No one under age 13 may provide or post any personal information on the Entrecard Sites. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

**Links to Other Sites**  
The Entrecard Sites contain links to other sites and services of third parties. Although we may initially visit these other sites or services that are so linked, we do not control the content that appear on these sites. In addition, the content on these sites or services may be constantly changing. We are not responsible for and assume no liability with respect to the content or privacy practices of such other sites.

These third party sites and services may have their own privacy policies and terms of use policies, or no policies at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing them with your personal information.

**Security Policy**  
Protecting your privacy and your information from loss, misuse and alteration while under our control is a top priority. We take reasonable precautions to insure the security of your information. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.

We may use third parties to assist us with business support functions, such as sending email messages, conducting market research and analyzing data among other things. These third parties have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to perform their functions and are not permitted to use it for other purposes. We require them to comply with our privacy policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Although we take these precautions, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

**User Agreement**  
By using any of the Entrecard Sites, you signify your acceptance of our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Entrecard Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
